A Guide to the Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music records FA1420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Audio, 1964-1983; 13; 0.65 Cubic Feet 1 phonograph box
  - The Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music - A Musical Celebration, Alice Tully Hall, New York City (As Recorded by National Public Radio), Tape 2, 1982 November 29; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 9978)
  - The Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music - A Musical Celebration, Alice Tully Hall, New York City (As Recorded by National Public Radio), Tape 3, 1982 November 29; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 9979)
  - The Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music - A Musical Celebration, Alice Tully Hall, New York City (As Recorded by National Public Radio), Tape 4, 1982 November 29; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 9980)
  - Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund Concert, National Public Radio - Part 1 and 2, 1983; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 9981)
  - Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund Concert, National Public Radio - Part 3 and 4, 1983; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 9982)
  - Andrew Newell - Performance of his work "Lost in Legends: 1. Mythical Gifts of Time From Time 2. Dance," Netherlands, 1982 January 21; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 9985)